{
    "id": "1afddbb92f754f78ab6630fd11a7587f",
    "title": "Magic, Magical, Classic, Classical",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2d3caa1a5527406cb78753bd85b432cd",
            "title": "Magic, Magical, Classic, Classical Etc.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Sneezing and a sore throat are .......................................... symptoms of a cold.",
                    "description": "Classic and classical can both mean standard or typical.",
                    "answers": [
                        "classic",
                        "classical",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The 1929 Packard is a ........................................... car.",
                    "description": "Classic and classical can both mean of the highest class or standard.",
                    "answers": [
                        "classic",
                        "classical",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ shoppers wait for special offers and discounts.",
                    "description": "Economical means frugal or thrifty.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Economic",
                        "Economical",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Good infrastructure is required for the ............................................. development of a country.",
                    "description": "Economic means financial.",
                    "answers": [
                        "economic",
                        "economical",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I got an ............................................. shock while I was vacuuming the carpet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "electric",
                        "electrical",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Children must not be allowed to play with ........................................... appliances.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "electric",
                        "electrical",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is learning ................................................. literature.",
                    "description": "Classical literature is literature that pertains to ancient Rome or Greece.",
                    "answers": [
                        "classic",
                        "classical",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................ parties are only interested in protecting their interests.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Politic",
                        "Political",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He graduated in .......................................... science.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "politic",
                        "political",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is not ............................................ to talk back to your elders.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "politic",
                        "political",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was a .......................................... experience.",
                    "description": "Magical means wonderful or surrealistic.",
                    "answers": [
                        "magic",
                        "magical"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The magician waved a ........................................... wand.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "magic",
                        "magical"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}